<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EpiDoum</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_add">contact</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="faq">Q&amp;As</string>
    <string name="prescription">Read the Medication Guide and, if available, the Patient Information Leaflet provided by your pharmacist before you start taking divalproex sodium and each time you get a refill.
        If you have any questions, ask your doctor or pharmacist.
        Take this medication by mouth once daily or as directed by your doctor.
        You may take it with food if stomach upset occurs. Do not crush or chew extended-release tablets.
        Doing so can release all of the drug at once, increasing the risk of side effects. Also, do not split the tablets unless they have a score line and your doctor or pharmacist tells you to do so.
        Swallow the whole or split tablet without crushing or chewing.

        The dosage is based on your age, weight, medical condition, response to treatment, and other medications you may be taking.
        Be sure to tell your doctor and pharmacist about all the products you use (including prescription drugs, nonprescription drugs, and herbal products). Use this medication regularly in order to get the most benefit from it. Remember to use it at the same time each day to keep the amount of medication in your blood constant.

If this medication is used for seizures, do not stop taking it without consulting your doctor. Your condition may become worse if the drug is suddenly stopped. Your dose may need to be gradually decreased.

Divalproex sodium does not relieve acute migraine headaches. Take other medications as directed by your doctor for acute attacks.

Inform your doctor if your condition does not improve.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact_us">contact_us</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>

    // FOR CHAT
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log Out</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="UserSettings">userSettings</string>
    <string name="main_settings_btn">Account Settings</string>
    <string name="displayname">DisplayName</string>
    <string name="userstatus">UserStatus</string>
    <string name="no_friends">no.friends</string>
    <string name="send_request">Send Request</string>
    <string name="decline_friend_request">decline friend request</string>
    <string name="will_be_user_image">will be user image</string>

</resources>
